https://www.kidswheels.com/privacy

Privacy
HomeRide On ToysReplacement PartsParts by BrandContact UsYour Shopping Cart
Register
You need to enable user registration from User Manager/Options in the backend of Joomla before this module will activate.
PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY
Our Commitment To Your Privacy and Data Security Because your privacy is important to us, we have installed safeguards to secure the credit card information you send us online. Our e-commerce site uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology supported by Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator/Communicator, and other popular browsers to protect your online transactions. SSL encrypts your credit card number, name, address, and phone number before they travel over the Internet. We also use additional technologies and measures to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure appropriate use of this information.Under no circumstances will we rent or sell information about our customers to any outside third party. All personally identifiable information is collected for our own purposes to help us better serve our Customers as well as informing our customers of new products or sales at KidsWheels.com.Should You wish not to receive Product Introductions or Up Dates please indicate so in the comments box of our order form.The Information We CollectThis Privacy Policy applies to all information collected or submitted on the KidsWheels.com web site. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages include:Name Address E-mail address Survey questions Phone number Credit card/Debit card informationOn some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected may include:Name Address Phone numberHow We Use InformationWe use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We may use your e-mail address to communicate with you, for example, to notify you of special offers or programs you might find of interest.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery.We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. We may also use these e-mail addresses to provide order status and order tracking information, and to respond to queries.You can register with our web site if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services.We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site.If you choose to register or receive products or materials from us, or to otherwise give us personal information, we may store some or all of that personal information and use it for marketing research and marketing purposes.We will never sell your personal information to any other company.In the event of a criminal investigation or a suspected illegal activity, we may be required by law enforcement agencies to share certain personal information.Finally, we never use or share personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.As adult supervision is required with all toys, we especially encourage the need for adult supervision with ride-on toys and motorized vehicles. Please ensure that your child wears a helmet with any ride-on vehicle. As KidsWheels is not the manufacturer of any of the items found on www.kidswheels.com, kidsWheels assumes no liability for personal injury incidents.KidsWheels reserves the right to refuse service at KidsWheels sole discretion with out recourse.Sales & Replacement Parts SupportPlease e-mail, This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
HomeShipping and ReturnsPrivacyUsage TermsAboutFAQ's/TroubleshootingSitemapRepair Instructions
Copyright © 2020.
KidsWheels.
Desktop Version
